What a battle!
真是一场苦战！
北京时间10月5号下午 中网第三轮
郑钦文本届第三次打进决胜盘
这场近三小时的硬仗
她怎样拿下来？
Good put away from Zheng.
郑钦文这一下收得漂亮
And just like that, breaks at love.
就这样 连下四分完成破发
高压收掉开局这一分
郑钦文随后2比0领先
3比1后却被追平
官方集锦未完整收录这段过程
抢七3比3后 她连拿四分
Oh, it drops in!
噢 这球落在界内！
So the first set goes to Zheng Qinwen.
首盘归郑钦文！
Coach likes that.
教练很满意
Crowd certainly likes it.
观众当然也很喜欢
Now confirmed that that ball did drop in.
现在确认了 这球确实落在界内
Extra cheer from the crowd in Beijing.
北京现场又响起一阵欢呼
So four last points won by Zheng in the tiebreak.
郑钦文拿下了抢七最后四分
盘点这记正手打向边线空当
对手追不到 郑钦文拿下首盘
但第二盘 她0比3落后
官方集锦没有完整收录这段丢分过程
So, breaks back, does Zheng.
郑钦文完成回破
That's one of the breaks back that she lost.
她追回了此前丢掉的一次破发
Oh, beautiful shot from Zheng there.
噢 郑钦文这一拍真漂亮
郑钦文追回到4比5
但布兹科娃的盘点 还是来了
Off to a third set we will go.
比赛进入决胜盘
Second straight match on this court today,
今天这块场地连续第二场比赛
that three sets is needed to decide a winner.
都要打满三盘才能决出胜负
Zheng Qinwen winning the opening set in the tiebreak.
郑钦文通过抢七拿下首盘
Bouzkova coming back to win the second, 6-4.
布兹科娃以6比4扳回第二盘
到了决胜盘 郑钦文没有送出破发点
先把自己的发球局守住
机会还要在一拍一拍里争
That's a really good service game from Zheng that time.
郑钦文这一局发球局打得真好
Oh, what a point!
噢 多精彩的一分！
Point of the match.
这就是全场最佳一分
Marie Bouzkova comes away with it.
布兹科娃拿下这一分
5比5 郑钦文从40比0打到平分
仍守住发球局 随后
第一个赛点被救
官方集锦没有收录这两段完整过程
再一次机会 来了
And it goes long!
这球出界了！
And it's Zheng Qinwen who gets it done!
郑钦文赢下了这场比赛！
And the crowd is loving it.
现场观众沸腾了
Her coach pleased as well.
她的教练也很满意
Pere Riba.
佩雷 里巴
What a battle!
真是一场苦战！
Bouzkova up for the challenge.
布兹科娃迎战到底
Final break of serve is the deciding moment,
最后这次破发决定了胜负
as Zheng Qinwen in front of her home Chinese crowd.
郑钦文站在中国主场观众面前
Big smile and almost a little bit of a dance there.
笑容灿烂 几乎要跳起舞来
Seven-six, four-six, seven-five.
7比6 4比6 7比5
Two hours, 54 minutes.
2小时54分钟
What a win for Zheng Qinwen,
郑钦文拿下一场精彩的胜利
who's through to the fourth round in Beijing.
晋级北京站第四轮
Certainly pleased with what they saw from Zheng Qinwen.
大家显然很满意郑钦文今天的表现
11个ACE 56记制胜分
也有33次非受迫失误
进攻有威力 赢下这一场
还得把最后的机会抓住
郑钦文闯进16强
下一轮面对恰拉耶娃
她能继续向前 打进八强吗？